Anything for Love is a romance, tv movie, comedy film directed by Terry Ingram.
Katherine, a high-powered executive who believes men are intimidated by her career, is persuaded by
her friend to create an internet dating profile claiming she is an executive assistant.
Katherine Benson, played by Erika Christensen.
Jack, played by Paul Greene.
Debbie, played by Ali Liebert.
Charles, played by Antonio Cupo.
Brooke, played by Nicole Major.
Edward Benson, played by Tom Butler.
Say Anything...
is a 1989 American teen romantic comedy-drama film written and
directed by Cameron Crowe in his feature directorial debut.
The film follows the romance between Lloyd Dobler (John Cusack), an average student, and Diane Court
(Ione Skye), the class valedictorian, immediately after their graduation from high school.
Say Anything...
was released theatrically in the United States on
April 14, 1989, by 20th Century Fox.
The film received highly positive reviews from critics.
In 2002, Entertainment Weekly named Say Anything...
the best modern romance film, and in 2012, ranked it number 11
on its list of the "50 Best High School Movies".
The film explores themes of romcom, lying, online dating.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.